sherrodbrown.com 2015-04-06

# Privacy Policy - U.S. Senator Sherrod Brown, Ohio - Official Campaign Website

At Friends of Sherrod Brown, we are putting forth every effort to ensure the privacy and security of information that you share with us online.

Our site links to a limited number of other websites. Friends of Sherrod Brown is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of these websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements for each website you visit. Friends of Sherrod Brown will occasionally update this privacy policy as changes to the site necessitate it.

**How do we protect your information?**

Our website has a number of security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. Computer systems have restricted access limited only to those persons and organizations necessary to its proper functioning. This access applies to all electronic and physical security measures. Highly sensitive data including credit card information is additionally secured through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Our servers are located in a locked, secure environment.

**How do we use the information you provide?**

We will use your e-mail address to provide you news and information about Friends of Sherrod Brown. We may also use your zip code and state to send you e-mail messages about upcoming campaign events or activities in your area.

We may also use the information that you provide online to contact you for other purposes or to solicit you for contributions. When you register or sign-up online, we may share your contact information with other like-minded Democratic candidates and organizations, and they may solicit you. However, we will not sell or exchange your credit card information to any other third party under any circumstances.

**When you contribute money online:**

We are required by federal law to collect and report to the Federal Election Commission the name, mailing address, occupation and employer of individuals whose contributions exceed $200 in an election cycle. These records are available to the public. However, they cannot be used by other organizations for fundraising. For additional information, visit the FEC website at http://www.fec.gov.

**When you sign one of our petitions:**

We treat your name, city, state, and any comments as public information. We may, for example, provide compilations of petitions, with your comments, to national leaders, without disclosing e-mail addresses. We may also make comments along with your city and state available to the press and public online.

**Information on Children:**

Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulations establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. Our site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13, and we have designed our sites to block our knowing acceptance of information from children under 13 whenever age-related information is requested.

[Parents with questions may e-mail us here](mailto:info@sherrodbrown.com).

**Unsubscribing from E-mail Communications:**

If you wish to unsubscribe from our communications, [please e-mail us here](mailto:info@sherrodbrown.com). We will regularly process these requests. To comply with federal election law, however, our contributor records will be continuously maintained in a separate secure database.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, corrections to the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site or your interaction with this website, [please contact us here](mailto:info@sherrodbrown.com).
